A GREAT STORY OF A NEW YORK PRIZEFIGHTER BATTLING
GIANT LUMBERJACKS TO WIN A GIRL'S LOVE!
The Knockout is a drama film directed by Lambert Hillyer.
A Lambert Hillyer silent romantic love triangle boxing sports lumberjack logging
melodrama about a world champion boxer who must retire due to an arm injury.
He becomes a lumberjack, and becomes involved with the daughter of the owner, but rivals sabotage their operation, and
the boxer has to return to the ring to save the owner from bankruptcy and win the hand of the daughter.
Sandy Donlin, played by Milton Sills.
Jean Farot, the daughter, played by Lorna Duveen.
Black Jack Ducane, played by John Kolb.
Mike Leary, played by Edward Lawrence.
Steve McKenna, played by Harry Cording.
Brown, played by Frank Evans.
The Knockout is a 1925 American silent drama film directed by
Lambert Hillyer and starring Milton Sills.
It was based on the novel The Come-Back by Morris DeCamp Crawford.
It was produced by and released by First National Pictures.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, lumberjack, boxing.
The tone is emotional.